Guide to the Kenneth E. Bailey Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Audio-Visual / Digital Material, Series V
  - Computer files
    - "Tadros Back Ups" (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - "Extra Programs (David)" (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - "Books Off-load" (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - "Books" (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - "Sara Per Lott 144 Letters" (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Unlabeled (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - "Display Writer (Backups)" (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - "Word Star 2000" (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - "86-82" (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - "Jesus and Women - Backup" (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - "Master 1: JMEE Section A, B, C, D, and Bibliography" (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - "Master 2: Jesus Through Middle Eastern Eyes" (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - "Master 3" (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - "Touch the Times Word 6.0" (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - "New Book #3 Feb. 14, 2006" (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - "JMEE A-D April 9" (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - "JMEE April 6, 2007" (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - "Fletcher's Book Copied February 2007" (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - "Greek Fonts; Hebrew Fonts; transferred into Word" (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - "World Map with Data Lines" (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - "BKJP #1, Dec. 30" (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - "Articles Backup Nov. 20" (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - "Mosha bar Repha Luke" (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - "Jesus Through Middle Eastern Eyes 2/07" (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - "Jesus Through Middle Eastern Eyes (Parables)" (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - "BKJP - Jacob & The Prod." (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - "Articles Backup Nov. 20 07" (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - "EMEU Appeal Letter for Church Mission's Committee" (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - "I Corinthians By Dr. Kenneth Bailey (color)" (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - "Microsoft Works for Windows; "Mainly Uphill" - Diaries 1986-1995. Bishop John Brown." (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - "Cross and Prodigal Revision (Dad) The Original" (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - "The Cross and the Prodigal (Reused Version) Ken Bailey 2004, Dec. 1 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - "EM Bailey's Diaries #1" (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - "The Cross and the Prodigal K.B. Bibliography" (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Unlabeled (Box 60, Folder 10-12)
  - DVDs
    - Jesus Interprets His Own Person (6 Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 1)
      DVD
    - Jesus Interprets His Own Cross (13 Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Paul's Hymn to Love (I Corinthians 13) (3 Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Decoding the DaVinci Code: Historical Reality vs. Murder Mystery Mythology (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - I Corinthians (A Middle Eastern Cultural View) (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Finding the Lost: The Prodigal Son: A Feature-Length Film; Arabic with English subtitles (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - The Lord's Prayer (A Middle Eastern Cultural View) (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Jesus and His Vision of Mission (8 Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Foundation Booklet (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Ken Bailey Artwork - 3 Separate Images and 1 Reference Comped Image (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - A Clear View of the Birth of Jesus (Four 30 minute DVD Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Parables of Jesus in Luke (A Middle Eastern Cultural View) (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - The Good Shepherd: A Theological Journey of 1,000 Years (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Understanding the Bible (2 Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Women in the New Testament (A Middle Eastern Cultural View) (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - The Beatitudes of Jesus (2 Lectures) (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Christian Leadership in the New Testament (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Transcriptions of audio and video presentations
    These transcriptions were prepared and compiled by Dale Bowne.
    - I Corinthians 13 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Beatitudes (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - A Clear View of Jesus' Birth (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Jesus Interprets His Own Cross (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Knowing God, Becoming God's People (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Luke 19:9-31 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - The Lord's Prayer (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Parables #1-13 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Staley Lecture: "This Lady is Not for Stoning", 1996 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Today's Truths from Ancient Corinth (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Understanding the Bible (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Other media
    - Theology | Poet | Prob. | Greek | OT | Pract (Box 63)
      Flashcards: Greek language grammar and vocabulary; bibliography notes